{
	"questions":[
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is a Functional Requirement?",
			"answers": [
				"The site should load in 3 seconds when the number of simultaneous users are > 10000",
				"The processing of each request should be done within 10 seconds",
				"Emails should be sent with a latency of no greater than 12 hours from such an activity.",
				"Authentication of user whenever he/she logs into the system."
			],
			"correct_ans": "4",
			"level": "3",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "What are code reviews good for?",
			"answers": [
				"Help contain a consistent programming style.",
				"Promise system structure degradation.",
				"Reduce record errors, and improve development methods.",
				"Data errors, duplication and inconsistency."
			],
			"correct_ans": "3",
			"level": "3",
			"team": "Hawk"
			
		},
		{
			"question": "What is \"Principal\" in software terms  ?",
			"answers": [
				"Implies a degree of importance that grants a design decision.",
				"A set of architectural design decisions that are applicable to a recurring design problem.",
				"Is the process of determining a software system's architecture from its implementation-level artifacts.",
				"An approach to software development where models rather than programs are the principal outputs of the development process."
			],
			"correct_ans": "1",
			"level": "3",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the pros of Usage of model-driven engineering?",
			"answers": [
				"Generating code automatically means that it is cheaper to adapt systems to new platforms.",
				"Savings from generating code may be outweighed by the costs of developing translators for new platforms.",
				"Allows systems to be considered at higher levels of abstraction.",
				"Answers 1 and 3 are correct."
			],
			"correct_ans": "4",	
			"level": "3",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is not a primary function of Peer Review?",
			"answers": [
				"Identify needed improvements.",
				"Daily Scrum meetings.",
				"Certify correctness.",
				"Encourage uniformity."
			],
			"correct_ans": "2",
			"level": "2",	
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is a Sprint Backlog in Scrum?",
			"answers": [
				"The back-end code that the developers have yet developed.",
				"A list of tasks identified by the Scrum team to be completed during the Scrum sprint.",
				"A method within Scrum that helps the developers be more productive.",
				"After finishing the project, a quick sprint is done to make sure that all the tasks have been completed."
			],
			"correct_ans": "2",
			"level": "2",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "When is it most expensive to add new features to a system?",
			"answers": [
				"During development.",
				"During maintenance.",
				"Whilst collecting requirments.",
				"It costs the same at every stage."
			],
			"correct_ans": "2",
			"level": "2",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is not a type of maintenance?",
			"answers":[
				"Corrective Maintenance.",
				"Adaptive Maintenance.",
				"Perfective Maintenance.",
				"Legacy Maintenance."
			],
			"correct_ans": "4",
			"level": "2",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which statement about the Waterfall methodology is incorrect?",
			"answers": [
				"Poor quality.",
				"Poor visibility.",
				"Testing starts from day one.",
				"Too risky."
			],
			"correct_ans": "3",		
			"level": "2",			
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "Program testing is ____",
			"answers": [
				"An effective way to show absence of bugs.",
				"Is not effective to show presence of bugs.",
				"Can't assure absence of bugs.",
				"None of the above."
			],
			"correct_ans": "3",
			"level": "2",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "In black box testing we _____ .",
			"answers": [
				"Know the software and test the actual code.",
				"Know the software and test functionality.",
				"Don't know the software and test actual code.",
				"Don't know the software and test functionality."
			],
			"correct_ans": "4",
			"level": "1",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is Agile?",
			"answers": [
				"Breakdown of project activities into linear sequential phases.",
				"Each phase depends on the deliverables of the previous one and corresponds to a specialization of tasks.",
				"Iterative approach to project management.",
				"none of the above."
			],
			"correct_ans": "3",
			"level": "1",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "In Agile:",
			"answers": [
				"Quality improves because testing starts from day one.",
				"Testing is the last phase in the process.",
				"It is very difficult to handle change.",
				"You've got schedule risk because you never know if you are going to make it until the end."
			],
			"correct_ans": "1",
			"level": "2",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is not a design pattern?",
			"answers": [
				"Decorator.",
				"Neighbor.",
				"Flyweight.",
				"Chain of Responsibility."		
			],
			"correct_ans": "2",
			"level": "1",
			"team": "Hawk"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is not type of requirements?",
			"answers": [
				"Functional Requirements.",
				"Non-Functional Requirements.",
				"Domain Requirements.",
				"Service Requirements."		
			],
			"correct_ans": "4",
			"level": "1",
			"team": "Hawk"
		}
	]
}